# SAMANDAR ABDUHAMITOV

## Flutter Developer

Tashkent, Uzbekistan | +998 91 207 79 78 | samandarabduhamitov@gmail.com

#### **CAREER SUMMARY:**

I have studied flutter technology intensive courses. I have been studying this field for more than 1 year, and my work experience is about 8 months. I participated in 2 real projects. But I didn't make a project from scratch. I am currently working on a new project myself. I've worked with PlayMarket and AppStore and posted projects and updated them.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

### **IT-Solutions Company**

Flutter Developer | December, 2021 - Present

- Increase productivity by using software to organize, track bug patches and add feature requests.
- Collaborate with other developers to update the application and create new features.

#### **TECHNOCITY**

SMM Marketelog | October, 2020 - December, 2020

- Create designed images for the post.
- Writing articles that attract customers.
- Gain experience from work.

## **RELEVANT PROJECTS:**

#### **UNG-Delivery**

January 2022 - April 2022

- Gasoline delivery service in Tashkent city.
- Adding useful features for users.
- Composed of three languages

#### U-GU (Sovetnik)

April 2022 - June 2022

- Online consulting service for legal entities and individuals.
- Accounting, lawyer and similar services.

## **EDUCATION:**

#### February - November | Najot Ta'lim IT Academy

Flutter Bootcamp Course

#### **SKILLS:**

- Bloc and Cubit for State management
- SOLID, DRY, KISS Clean Architecture
- HTTP and DIO methods for API
- Responsive UI for all phones